<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mombasa Tour</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="beach_fragment">Beachs</string>
    <string name="h_site_fragment">Sites</string>
    <string name="hotel_fragment">Hotels</string>
    <string name="tourist_attraction_sites_fragment">Attractions</string>
    <string name="diani_beach_facts">Lying on the Indian Ocean approximately 30km south of Mombasa city, Diani beach is the most popular beach associated with plenty of sunlight that allows you to indulge and experience tranquility that you will not find anywhere else.</string>
    <string name="nyali_beach_facts">Located in the upmarket neighborhood of Nyali, the easy accessibility makes this beach rank highly amongst the top beaches in Mombasa. The good thing about Nyali beach is that it’s pristine, calm and quiet. Apparently, the crowds here are relatively few especially if you want to be on a laid back beach that allows privacy. The beauty is outstanding; there are hundreds of palm trees and plenty of beach sports.</string>
    <string name="bamburi_beach_facts">Located about 10 km from Mombasa city centre, Bamburi beach has several beachfront hotels, apartments and villas. The famous ‘Pirates’ (Jomo Kenyatta Public beach) which is Mombasa’s and Kenya’s largest public beach is located on this stretch of Bamburi beach. If you love an active and lively beach; Pirates is a good option. You can relax, swim, catch up with friends or participate in beach and water sports, the beach fronts facing hotels are less busy and quiet as most people tend to remain on the pirates stretch.</string>
    <string name="shanzu_beach_facts">After Bamburi beach, the next beach further up is Shazu beach. Top world class resorts are located in the posh neighborhood of Shanzu that is well known to be peaceful and quiet. Shanzu beach is located approximately 14km from Mombasa CBD and has on numerous occasions, won the hearts of many as one of the top beaches in Mombasa. Hotels on this stretch are closely packed together; there are also plenty of bars and relaxation spots where you can have some time off to reflect and indulge with nature.</string>
    <string name="tiwi_beach_facts">Tiwi is a quiet beach tucked away in Kwale County approximately 18km from Mombasa City. If you are tired, stressed and want absolute silence, this is the place to be. For holidaymakers who simply want to unwind and keep it low; there are numerous good hotels on this stretch of the beach that incorporates a countryside feel.</string>
    <string name="copacabana_beach_facts">Mtwapa is a famous town located 16km north of Mombasa city famous for its vibrant nightlife and party scene. Mtwapa is a tourist magnet suburb loved by both foreign and local tourists. From the beach, you get the chance to enjoy exotic views of the Indian Ocean and the Mtwapa creek. There are numerous villas, private residences, restaurants and bars where you can go and have fun.</string>
    <string name="fort_jesus_facts">Fort Jesus is undoubtedly one of Mombasa’s popular and most visited historical sites. The gigantic structure that lies in the CBD next to Old Town was built by the Portuguese in 1593-1596. While here, you get the chance to step back into history and get a glimpse of how the battle to control Mombasa played out centuries ago.</string>
    <string name="mombasa_old_town_facts">Located on the south eastern side of Mombasa Island, old town covers about 180 acres with predominant ancient buildings that define the city’s history.</string>
    <string name="mombasa_tusks_facts">These two giant elephant tusks found along Moi Avenue are one of the main Mombasa attractions. Anyone who comes to Mombasa always wants to visit and take a photo at the famous tusks.</string>
    <string name="hindu_temples_facts">Mombasa has large Hindu temples where you can learn more about the Hindu religion. With proper arrangements in place, you can be allowed to get inside and see the unique Hindu stone carvings as well as idols that adorn different parts of the temples.</string>
    <string name="bombolulu_workshops_facts">Bombolulu workshop located about 15 minutes north of the CBD off Mombasa-Malindi highway is a great place to be. Managed by the Association for the Physically Disabled (APDK), this key tourist attraction is a great site you must visit while in Mombasa.l</string>
    <string name="blueroom_facts">This is a great spot to try if looking for African classics peppered with European influences. With a charming Afro-American vibe, the Blue Room offers burgers and milkshakes alongside their traditional curries, providing a home-from-home for tourists.</string>
    <string name="galaxy_chinese_facts">If you are longing for authentic noodles, chow mein, or rice that doesn’t come automatically paired with a Kenyan fish curry, then Galaxy Chinese should be high on your list of places to visit.</string>
    <string name="la_marina_facts">La Marina prepares perfectly cooked seafood right on the beach. Perfect for a magical evening by the water, this particular Mombasa favorite oozes romance, offering the opportunity to depart from the beach and take a ride in the restaurant’s dhow, the traditional Arab sailing vessel.</string>
    <string name="thalassa_facts">Thalassa restaurant is locally favored for its private pool and stunning panoramic views of the winding Tudor Creek, providing a perfect place to relax in the hot, tropical climate.</string>
    <string name="shehnai_facts">Shehnai Restaurant promises to evoke the old spice route that connected India and the East Coast of Africa, promising you a romantic cultural journey without ever having to leave Mombasa. Named after the Indian instrument of the same name, Shehnai offers a vast selection of premium spices perfectly matched to the sustainably sourced ingredients.</string>
    <string name="tamarind_facts">One of several Tamarind ventures in Mombasa specializing in sea-to-table produce, this ambient venue has deliciously cooked seafood which is considered to be the signature creation.</string>
    <string name="moorings_facts">The Moorings restaurant boat is located on the north side of Mombasa and has an incredible seaside location, floating among the mangroves. As one of the oldest restaurants in Mombasa, and considered to be one of the best, The Moorings serves a selection of fresh seafood platters with sides of new potatoes and freshly cooked vegetables.</string>
    <string name="haller_park_facts">Haller Park is a hit with animal lovers. Formerly called Bamburi Nature Trail, this inspirational project began in 1971, when Dr. René Haller transformed the abandoned limestone quarries here into a thriving nature reserve. Dr. Haller increased the mineral content of the soil, planted trees, added a fish farm, and created a wildlife park where each animal has a function within the flourishing ecosystem. Wildlife found here includes giraffes, Cape buffalo, zebras, waterbucks, and hippos.</string>
    <string name="mombasa_marine_national_park_facts">One of the busiest of Kenya\'s offshore reserves, Mombasa Marine National Park protects mangroves, seagrass beds, sandy beaches, and coral reef. Diving and snorkeling are popular activities - especially north of Mombasa, from Mtwapa Creek south to the entrance of Likoni.</string>
    <string name="mamba_village_facts">Mamba Village Centre in Nyali is East Africa\'s largest crocodile farm. Visitors can learn about the life cycle and behavior of these fascinating amphibians, and the center also offers horseback riding and a botanical garden with an aquarium.</string>
    <string name="go_kart_facts">Mombasa Go-Kart is a hit with speedsters and kids of all ages. Zoom around the smooth concrete track in go-karts, bounce around on the off-road buggies, or learn to dig in a Bobcat excavator.</string>
    <string name="wasini_island_facts">Generally reached by dhow, Wasini Island is a popular day trip from Mombasa. Dolphins regularly cruise these waters, and passengers can stop to snorkel and dive the coral reefs along the way. The island itself is tiny - only five square kilometers. Sightseeing opportunities include visiting Wasini Village, strolling around the coastal scrub where ancient Swahili ruins lie, exploring the exposed coral gardens, and dining on fresh seafood.</string>
    <string name="kisite_facts">South of Wasini Island, Kisite-Mpunguti Marine National Park is a popular spot for snorkeling, diving, and dolphin spotting - usually from the decks of a traditional dhow. The park encompasses four small islands surrounded by fish-rich coral reef. Dolphins frolic in the Shimoni Channel, and humpback whales swim these waters between August and October.</string>
    <string name="watamu_facts">About 112 kilometers from Mombasa, Watamu is a Swahili fishing village that has blossomed into a small beach resort and offers superb snorkeling and diving. The coast is broken into three coves divided by rocky headlands. Offshore from Watamu is the southern part of the Malindi Marine National Reserve.</string>
</resources>
